

### Yuri Ramos

# My Objective

I am a person who is always looking for something new. I founded an online consulting firm in September 2014 aimed at changing the practices of the middle Health & Fitness in digital media and live new challenging experiences. Currently, working as front-end developer with 5 years of experience, working with WEBAPPS, Single-page Applications, Cross-browser responsive pages, Bootstrap and others. Focused on mastering the library React.JS + redux to develop Progressive WebApps.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Front-end Developer [January 2015 - Currently]

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

One of project leaders of the channels TV GLOBOSAT group.

One of the responsibles for the migration of the tv channels that are not responsive yet. Responsible for the responsive projects Premiere Combate and Channel Sexy Hot.

#### Front-end Lead Developer [June 2014 - August 2015]

Remote Wor

Act as leader of the new project CAPGOV, collaborating to create a new page into the context of current technologies and improving the position on google by SEO. Using drupal CMS as content manager.

# Founder, Marketing Manager, Project Manager, Full-Stack Developer and BI [September 2014 - March 2016]

SoulFit was an online fitness consultancy that delivered to their customers a product encapsulated as "SoulFit Kit" that included:

Curitiba, Brazi

Rio de Jameiro, Brazi

Rio de Jameiro, Brazi

Personalized Training; Personalized Diet; Ebooks made by us to help our customers achieve their goals. With minimum 3-months plan, we deliver to our customers feedbacks biweekly and monthly. Accordingly to their results if it's necessary we made changes in their diet and training plan.

### Education

#### Computer Systems [August 2015 - Currently]

Federal University Fluminense- UFF

#### Computer Science [August 2010 - January 2015]

Federal University of Rio De Janeiro - UFRJ

### Skills

Proficiency	Professional
HTML5/CSS	Programming
SASS	UX/UI
Webpack/Gulp	TDD
Mongo/SQL	Davasasi
Worldon 265	Personal
Javascript	Creative

## **Personal Information**

Name Yuri Pereira Ramos

Birth June 12, 1991

Nacionality Brazilian

Nationality Rio de Janeiro

Languages English(fluent), Spanish

(intermediate), Portuguese

# **Recent Projects**

TesteDNA

Working developing the front-end of a startup e-Commerce in the field of parternity test and DNA tests.

# **Highlights**

- Self-Didact
- Good Oratory
- Sociability
- Proactivity
- Ágile Development (Methodologies Scrum e Kanban)

### Contact

Address Av. Prefeito Dulcidio Cardoso, 2500, bloco 2 apto 1501.

Phone +5521 97141-7218

Email yuri.pramos@gmail.com

Web www.yuriramos.com